おあいにくさま　返り討ちだね。
Do you need something?
反撃すらできずに死んで行くよ あんた達。
I heard that you're leaving tomorrow. You're abandoning the election and your son?
クッヘヘヘ　そうか？ あ？
That bald fool!
すげぇ軽いぜ？ そんなパンチじゃ
Why did he tell her? Why don't you stay and see this through?
何万発　弾こうが 俺達は殺せねえよ。
We already know the election's outcome.
ハハ！　知ってるよ　それ 痩せ我慢っていうんだよね。
I've had my fun. Meeting that Leorio guy was the best part.
ハハ…　ミットにボールが 入った　はるか後に振ってるよ！ 言っとくけど まだ本気じゃないぜ。
We're down to four candidates.
We don't know the outcome. That's what I'm saying.
See? You do understand.
ハハっ 体が意識に　ついて来てないね。
You can tell yourself that until the day this ends.
身体能力の差は歴然！
Wait!
何で埋める気？　銃？　頭数？
What do you want?
へへっ　知恵と経験かね。
I'll do as you say. What should I do?
フ。
You don't sound too happy about it.
ん？ いつの間にか 周りを覆ってる
I don't know what Pariston is thinking.
煙…　ガスか？　毒？ それとも催眠？ いや　奴らも中にいる
How do I beat him? Except you've never done anything
I've told you to do...
これも何かの能力か？ フッ　怖いか？
Okay, I'll start with what Pariston's thinking, then.
逃げてもいいんだぜ。
He doesn't want to win.
ハハっ！　ってことは あんた達は逃げないんだ？
But he doesn't want to lose, either.
つまり　これは煙幕ね
That's what makes him strong.
煙に乗じて攻撃する気か
What? How can that be?
まっ　お手並み拝見しよっかな
Yeah, I know.
そら　来た！
Common sense tells you that people
who want to win are stronger, right?
なっ！ うっ！　うぅ…。
Nothing wrong with that. You're right.
うっ！
And being right makes you predictable.
ギョっとすると　体　固まるだろ。
That goes especially for when you want to win
同じ相手に　何度も 通用することじゃねえが
a game where you're trying to secure votes.
一発で十分。
Game?
どこが？　全然　痛くねえ。
See? You thought I was being disrespectful, right?
不意を突かれたのは　認めるけど ダメージなんて　ほとんどないぜ。
You're mad because you're big on morals,
balance, and sticking to the manual.
あっ？
Look at me. You're failing to act like a dog.
何だ　これ？
You're just being yourself.
さぁ　何だろうな。
Pariston is familiar with both sides
of you, so he knows that.
答えろ。 答えろ！
He knows exactly what you're
thinking and what you'll do next.
今度は　怒りで周りが見えてねえ。
He's damn good, right? Then what do I do? I told you...
お前をこかすのなんざ　超簡単！
If I tell you what to do, you'll never listen.
うぅ！
How many times must we go through this?
うら　こら！ 消えた？
Okay, I'll tell you what happens
if the game continues as is.
どこだ!? 時間です。 うっ。
First, you and Pariston will be the ones
remaining after the next vote.
利息がつきます。
In the two-candidate vote after
that, first and second will flip.
フンっ！ どんな能力でも関係ないね。
And that's what will keep happening.
ぶっちぎれば　いいんだからよ！
Pariston will probably try
to lower the turnout rate.
「絶」には 対応できないようだな。
Why? Like I said... He doesn't want to win or lose.
ポットクリンが　ついていれば 大まかな位置は分かりますから
He's just looking to have fun. He's like Netero and me.
追っかけて　速攻　囲んで ジ・エンドですよ。
Well, I get bored a lot more quickly...
けど　あれって　お前から 離れ過ぎたら効果がないんだろ？
But he has more patience. Of the four remaining candidates,
Pariston is the only one
利息のカウントは止まりますが 消えは　しないっす。
who carries on Netero's will.
俺が接近すれば また時計は動きだしますし
You have no right to say that!
あれなら　トリタテンに 変わらなくても楽勝っす。
You're only jealous of him.
もう奴の動きは見切りました。 バカタレが！ たとえ　球種が分かっても
Were you that fond of the dirty old man?
俺達じゃ打ち損じるから 問題なんだろうが。
Shut your mouth! Don't get too full of yourself!
あとは　あいつと相性のいい 術者に任せりゃいい。
You just have to tell me the day
when this election will end, you stupid vagabond!
そうっすね ゴン達のほうが気になるし。
Okay, I can do that...
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
But before this is over, you
should learn to act in character. You're impossible to talk to.
チクショ こいつ　全然　振り切れねえ 速いだけじゃ通用しない
The day Netero blew himself up, one hundred large airships belonging
to the Hunter Association
これが「念」か
set off for East Gorteau.
スピード以外の力が　いる！
There's no record of their departure. All records show that they're
in hangars for maintenance.
ここにカイトがいる。
And they're all probably about to hatch.
もう　お前達の知っている 彼では　ないぞ。 大丈夫 絶対　俺達が治してみせる。
Pariston plans to have some fun with them, now that he has such a huge playground. The day the election ends will be
the day of the next Hunter Exam.
「ホテル・ラフレシア」。
However, if the Commandments are reformed, the situation will change slightly.
ある一定以上の ダメージを敵に与えると
You'll have to figure out the rest yourself.
そいつをここに 閉じ込めることができる。
Aren't you a Hunter?
籠から出ると 元の大きさに戻る
Now, first, we have comments from the
candidates who did not qualify.
用心してくれ 「念」は使えないが それでも手ごわい
First, I would like to thank everyone
who supported me. Thank you. And if possible, going forward, I would ask those who had
faith in me to give your votes to Cheadle.
おそらく兵隊アリの訓練に 利用されていたんだと思う。
We will now begin the speeches
from the candidates. There is one thing to note.
近づく奴を機械的に攻撃して来る。
Everyone who's gathered inside the hall today will be asked to stay until the 13th
chairman has been selected.
あっ！
Anyone inside? Only Tsubone and Canary.
カイトに殴られるの。
How's Master Alluka?
反射が　よけようとか 防ごうとするとこを 力ずくで抑えて わざと攻撃を食らってる感じだ。 マジか いくら機械的に 決められた動きとはいえ
It's possible that we will
continue to have multiple ties, but we've arranged for all necessary provisions, so you can rest easy repeating the vote as
many times as necessary, be it for hours or days.
今のゴンが　数分やそこらで
Let me repeat myself.
看破できるような レベルじゃねえはずだ きっと他に　どうしていいか 分からないんだ
You may not leave this hall until the
13th chairman has been selected.
俺達が作り出した 目の前の現実
Now, we'll start with a speech from
the candidate in fourth, Mizaistom.
次も
To eliminate Pariston, I will
serve as a sacrificial lamb.
そして左
I'll make this quick.
フェイントを入れて… ハハハ… ホントに機械みたいだ
Of the four candidates on stage, I believe the one most qualified to be chairman is Cheadle.
カイトは　こんなに弱くない
I won't say that I'm not willing
to become chairman.
カイトの拳は…　もっと痛い！
But it isn't my time. First, I must train the Hunters under me, and work to become a Triple Hunter.
ごめんね　カイト。
That's all I have to say.
俺達のせいで　こんな…。
What should I say?
少し　休んでいいよ。
Next, we have the candidate
in third, Cheadle-san. All yours.
後は俺達に任せて。
I'll also make this quick. Ladies and gentlemen, I believe the 13th chairman
あっ！
That's all I have to say.
レベル２ ゴンには見えてねえだろうが
What is Cheadle up to?
カイトに触れると発動するようだ。
I'm not gonna be elected.
クリアするには　かなり 高度な戦闘技術が必要になる。
I don't even want to be elected. But I guess I should say what I want.
カイト自身の「念」は 俺の能力で封じてあるから
My focus right now isn't this election, anyway.
あれは　カイトを操っている者の 念能力。
Okay... Thank you.
気をつけろよ。
Next, we have the candidate
in second, Leorio-san.
もう一度　触れると攻撃して来る。
All yours.
どうすれば…。
You aren't smiling anymore, Pariston.
どうやって止めたの？ 相応の深手を彼に与えた。
I won't let you have your way! Huh?
やむを得なかったとはいえ すまない。
Leorio-san, could you please speak?
近づかなければ　あっちから 仕掛けて来ることはない。
Leorio-san!
カイト…。
Ah! Me?
もう　ちょっと待ってて。
Nope, I'm drawing a blank.
すぐに戻す。
What am I doing up here? Forget it.
キルア。
If elected chairman, I'll treat the
Association like it belongs to me!
あいつは…　俺１人でやる！
My first command will be to order
all of you to help save Gon!
キルア。 お前を見た時も感じたが お前ら２人
This isn't where I should be right now.
一体　この短期間で何をしたんだ？ 俺達は別に…。
Well, it isn't like I could help
Gon if I were with him...
何かしたのは　相手のほうさ。
He's... Gon is fighting for his life now. He's a buddy. A friend.
そして ゴンが念能力を失ってから
But I only found out recently.
２９日が過ぎた 本当に　いいのかよ ２人を同行させても。 じいさんとの約束を 破ることになるぜ。 問題ありません。 あの選抜試験では ＮＧＬへ行く者を決めたのです。
While I was studying for myself, drinking, moving from place to place, jerking off, entertaining women, and surfing the Internet...
これから我々が向かう先は 東ゴルトー共和国ですから。
He was fighting for others. Alongside the former chairman and their allies.
へりくつにしか聞こえねえけどな。 それでは　連れて行くのを やめますか？
One of them has put his life
on the line to save Gon.
少なくとも　てめぇの尻拭いは てめぇで　できるさ。
All I could do was talk to Gon.
うん　キルアは　ともかく ゴンのほうは　どうでしょうか？
That's all I can do.
あの時の動きと気迫 確かに目を見張りましたが
So if I become chairman,
I won't stop talking to you.
それ以降のゴンには 全く覇気が感じられません。
Please help save Gon!
修行をしてても 集中力不足は歴然です。
Use your heads! If you have an idea, take action!
能力の上下に　かなりのムラが あると思うのですが。
If there's something I can do, tell me. I'll do anything!
あいつが本領を発揮するのは 本番　土壇場。
Ging... I think I understand why you
didn't avoid his punch.
ここ数週間のやる気のなさは むしろ　バネだと思うね。 バネ？ じっくり ため込んでるってことよ。
Even from that moment,
you saw something in him.
全てをぶつけるためにな。
I'm fine with having him as chairman.
まぁ　すぐに分かるさ。 明日には ゴンの「念」が復活するし
Damn, I think I said more than I needed to.
敵も目前だ！
Forget the part about jerking off. I'm done.
[TV]　ここ最近の 東ゴルトーの急激な動きには 一体　どのような意図が あるのでしょうか？
If we're there to support him, I'm sure he'll make a good chairman.
１０日後に 首都ペイジンで開催される 建国記念大会への国民全員参加を 強く呼びかけましたが…。
Finally, we have the candidate
in first place, Pariston-san. All yours.
[TV]　そうですね
Everyone, please be quiet!
過去にも　全員参加の集会は 何回か行われています。
It's over, Pariston.
[TV]　ただし　今回のように 大会を３日にわたって行い
It doesn't matter what you say.
赤ん坊や病人まで含めて 限りなく１００％に近い国民を 徴集するのは
My eighty-seven votes,
Mizai's seventy-two votes, and the fifty-seven independent votes
異例中の異例ですね 今までの大会とは
will be added to Leorio's ninety-five. That gives him three hundred, eleven votes.
全く目的が違うと考えるのが 自然でしょうね。
He'll have over fifty percent of the vote.
[TV]　例えば　どんな理由が 考えられますか？
The 13th chairman will be Leorio.
[TV]　そうですね 後継者の初披露と
Everyone, please quiet down.
政権譲渡が同時に発表されれば 強い効果があるでしょうね。
Refrain from using mobile phones.
[TV]　しかし　総帥が 自ら権力の座から 降りるなんてことは 考えにくいですし
Um, in a moment, I'm going to get loud.
もしかしたら　別の何かから 目をそらさせるための
Everyone, you can continue
talking on the phone.
陽動作戦かもしれません。
This is the true Hunter spirit.
[TV]　とにかく　１０日後 全世界の視線が 東ゴルトーに集まります。 コルトの予想では
Once this election ends, I promise to
do everything I can to help Gon-kun.
その大会期間中に 全国民の選別が行われる。
However, we must keep that matter
separate from the election.
目覚めた者を どう使うかは分からないが
Of the remaining candidates,
the one most qualified to be chairman
９９％の人間は その選別で死に至る。
is Mizaistom-san.
その前に　絶対　阻止する。
Heart Is Valuable There's something I've learned
リミットは　１０日間。
after serving as Chairman Netero's
Vice Chairman for three years.
ところで　じいさんは何してんの？
Heart Is Valuable
すでに　東ゴルトー内に 潜伏しているとメールがあったが
There are three conditions a chairman needs. First is combat ability.
それ以来　音信不通だ。
This is an absolute necessity,
given our job requirements.
もしかして もう殺られてんじゃないの？
During the recent crisis, this was evident.
事前の打ち合わせでは 「今日中に連絡がなければ
Second is experience.
そう判断して行動しろ」と 言われている。 [TEL]
Wisdom comes from experience! As a Hunter, you can never have
too many years of experience. Why?
うわさをすれば　会長からです。
Why do I feel so irritated when he's talking?
あのじじい　地獄耳だ　絶対。
And the third is caliber. I know why...
全て　お見通しです。
I understand him.
あなた達２人が来ることも
He never says what he truly thinks.
モラウさんの陰口もね。
There aren't too many people who make you think
護衛軍を王から引き離してくれ。
that the Association would be in good
hands if they were chairman.
決行は　大会前夜　０時ジャスト。
Cheadle lacks combat ability. Leorio-san lacks experience.
地獄耳のじじいより」。
Stop... Don't let emotions get the best of me.
つくづく　恐ろしい　じいさんだな。
And I lack all three!
名残惜しいが 約束の３０日が今　切れちまった。
I need to figure out what he's after.
それじゃあ 俺様は　消えるとするぜ！ じゃあ　またな！ バッハハイ！
I believe that Mizaistom-san is the only
one possessing all three qualities.
さぁ　これで 元通り「念」は使えるぜ。
One hundred and twenty of Pariston's two
hundred ninety are Association Hunters. Thirty of the votes come from
試してみろよ。
the investigative and administrative
departments he heads.
ゴン　あいにくだが
Pariston is able to control those votes
俺は　まだ　お前を認めてねえぜ。
as he likes without any signs or speeches.
お前の覚悟を見せてもらおうか。 俺をカイトの仇だと思って 撃って来な。
We will now move on to the
debate among the candidates.
もしも　それが腑抜けた一発なら
Pariston's speech will create a split
今すぐ　代わりのハンターを呼ぶ。
among the independents, who were all
most likely leaning toward Leorio.
まったく　師匠も人が悪いぜ
I'm guessing this is how it will look.
とっくに認めてるくせによ ゴン　見せてやれよ。 おめぇの「ジャジャン拳」。
But that would just push the
election out another vote, which matches our goal.
本気でいいの？
Will something change during the debate?
ふざけんな！ 少しでも手加減したら てめぇは　不合格だ！
Fine, then... I'll figure this out myself!
分かった。
Can I go first, then?
んっ！
As I said earlier, I'm not interested
in becoming chairman. No, you said that you wouldn't say
you're not willing to become chairman.
ゴン…　もう十分だ。
But if Leorio remains, the votes previously cast for myself
and the openly anti-Pariston Mizai
だろ？　おっさん。
will go to Leorio.
あ…　あぁ。 あっ。
He'll hold on to Teradein's anti-Zodiac votes, and the Morel votes are also anti-Pariston.
キルア　サンキュー！ ごめんなさい　モラウさん！
Meaning that they'll never switch to Pariston.
ホントに　殺しちゃうとこだった。
Got it, Mizai? Yeah, I understand.
ふっ　ハハハ…。 ハハハ…！
Defeating Pariston is the ultimate goal.
参ったぜ　完敗だ！
As a Crime Hunter, I trust my instinct.
イカレ具合も 言うことなしの一人前だよ。 ここからは　別行動だ。
There's no proof, and it's entirely possible
that his hands are clean. However...
それぞれのやり方で 指令を全うしよう。
He definitely has underground ties.
ゴンとキルアは 望み通り　ネフェルピトーを。
We can't let him run rampant within
the Association any longer.
ナックルとシュートは モントゥトゥユピーって奴　担当で。
Since it appears that not even
Netero could rein him in...
俺とノヴは　シャウアプフを。 健闘を祈る！
This election is where we must...
その日まで　残り１０日
And so, the eighth vote for
the 13th chairman begins.